Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
José de Rivera papers
- Photographs, 1930-1985, Series 7:; (Box 4-7, OV 9-OV 10; 1.7 linear feet)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #72, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #74, Construction #75, and Construction #76, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #79 and Construction #87, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #98, 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #88, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #89, Construction #92, and Construction #94, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #107, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #110, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #115, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #116, Construction #117, and Construction #118, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #118A, Construction #120, and Construction #121, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #125, Construction #126, and Construction #127,1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #132 and Construction #133, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #134 and Construction #137,1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #140, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #141, Construction #142, and Construction #144, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #145 and Construction #147, circa 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #152 and Construction #153A, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #151 and Construction #157, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #158, 1974-1984, (6 folders) (Box 5, Folder 12-17)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #160, Construction #161, and Construction #163, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #167, Construction #170, and Construction #173, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #179, Construction #180, and Construction #182-2, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Unidentified Bronze Sculptures, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #183, Construction #184, and Construction #186,1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #187, Construction #188, and Construction #189,1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #190, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Construction #193 and Construction #200, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Photographs of Art Work: Unidentified Sculpture, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Slides of Art Work, 1958-1960, undated, (6 folders) (Box 5, Folder 28-33)
  - Photographs of Art Work by Others, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Exhibition Installations at the Grace Borgenicht Gallery, New York, 1955, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 35-36)
  - Photographs of Exhibition Installation at the Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Photographs of Exhibition Installation at the Whitney Museum of American Art, New York, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Exhibition Installations, 1981, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - An Oversized Rolled Photograph of Art Work: [Female Figure], undated, (from Box 4, Folder 13) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - An Oversized Rolled Photograph of Art Work: [Abstract Form], undated, (from Box 4, Folder 14) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - An Oversized Rolled Photograph of Art Work: [Abstract Human Form], undated, (from Box 4, Folder 15) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - An Oversized Rolled Photograph of Art Work: Bust and Owl, 1930, (from Box 4, Folder 28) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Six Oversized Photographs of José de Rivera, undated, (from Box 4, Folder 8) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: [Abstract Form], undated, (from Box 4, Folder 14) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: [Abstract Human Form], undated, (from Box 4, Folder 15) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Three Oversized Photographs of Art Work: [Abstract Sculptures in Marble], undated, (from Box 4, Folder 17) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Four Oversized Contact Sheets of Photographs of Art Work: Miscellaneous Stainless Steel Sculptures, undated, (from Box 4, Folder 21) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Bust and Owl, 1930, (from Box 4, Folder 28) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Form Synthesis [Bust], 1935, (from Box 4, Folder 31) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Flight, 1937, (from Box 4, Folder 35) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Bas-Relief for Soviet Pavilion, New York World's Fair, 1939, (from Box 4, Folder 36) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Blue, White, Yellow, 1942, (from Box 4, Folder 47) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Black and Red Construction, 1942, (from Box 4, Folder 48) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Three Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Construction in Black and Yellow, 1945-1949, (from Box 4, Folder 52) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Yellow, Black, 1946, (from Box 4, Folder 54) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Light Sculpture for Andrew Geller Shoe Salon, 1947, (from Box 4, folder 55) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Photographs of Art Work: [Aluminum Sculpture with Red, Black, Yellow Pigment], 1947-1950, (from Box 4, Folder 56) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: En Route, S. S. Argentina Dining Salon, 1949, (from Box 4, Folder 60) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Bas-Relief, 1950, (from Box 4, Folder 62) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Black and Red Construction, 1951, (from Box 4, Folder 65) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Construction in Blue and Black [I], 1951, (from Box 4, Folder 66) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Construction in Blue and Black [II], 1951, (from Box 4, Folder 67) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: [Stainless Steel Construction], 1951, (from Box 4, Folder 68) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Continuum, 711 Third Avenue, New York City, 1956, (from Box 4, Folder 81) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - An Oversized Photograph of Art Work: Sculpture for 110 William Street Corporation, New York City, 1959, (from Box 4, Folder 90) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Four Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Model Ship designs for the U. S. Navy, circa 1944, (from Box 4, Folder 50) (Box OV 9)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work: Miscellaneous Stainless Steel Sculptures, undated, (from Box 4, Folder 21) (Box OV 10)